K. SRI VAISHNAVI

Banking Analyst

- O Hyderabad, India 500086
- 8939292838
- vaishuvandhana@gmai



Knowledgeable and dedicated customer service professional with extensive experience in Retail Banking industry. Solid team player with outgoing, positive demeanor and proven skills in establishing rapport with clients. Motivated to maintain customer satisfaction and contribute to company success. Specialize in quality, speed and process optimization. Articulate, energetic and results-oriented with exemplary passion for developing relationships, cultivating partnerships and growing businesses.



Skills

- Account management
- Professional telephone demeanor
- Complaint resolution
- Receiving support
- Report preparation
- Retail materials management
- Recordkeeping strengths
- Strategic sales knowledge
- CRM
- International sales support



Work History

2019-01 - 2022-05

Teaching Professional

Bharath Polytechnic college, Chennai

- Enhanced student knowledge of technology by integrating various web-based applications for research and assignments.
- Graded and evaluated student assignments, papers and course work.
- Planned and implemented integrated lessons to meet national standards.
- Communicated frequently with parents, students and faculty to provide feedback and discuss instructional strategies.

Teaching Professional

Venkateshwara Polytechnic college, Vellore

- Enhanced student knowledge of technology by integrating various web-based applications for research and assignments.
- Graded and evaluated student assignments, papers and course work.
- Planned and implemented integrated lessons to meet national standards.
- Communicated frequently with parents, students and faculty to provide feedback and discuss instructional strategies.

2016-05 - 2017-11

Banking Customer Service Representative

HDB Financial services, Chennai

- 1) Attending client calls for prime HDB customers as a personal banker.
- 2) Helping customers to choose the right product based on their needs as part of my sales target.
- 3) Achieving sales target on a monthly basis and also helping my team members to meet the target.
- 4) Delivered excellent customer service, resulting in consistent 100% customer satisfaction rating.
- 5) Reached out to customers after completed sales to suggest additional service or product purchases.
- 6) Communicated professionally with colleagues, freelancers and clients.

2015-04 - 2016-04

Teaching Professional

Saraswathi Vel Polytechnic college, Vellore

- Enhanced student knowledge of technology by integrating various web-based applications for research and assignments.
- Graded and evaluated student assignments, papers and course work.
- Planned and implemented integrated lessons to meet national standards.
- Communicated frequently with parents, students and faculty to provide feedback and discuss instructional strategies.



Education

2009-05 - 2013-05

Bachelors of Engineering: Electrical And Electronics Engineering

Vinayaga Mission University - Salem

2013-06 - 2015-06

Masters of Engineering: Power Electronics And Drives

Arunai Engineering College - Thiruvannamalai

2021-06 - Current

MBA: Finance And HR

Bharathidasan University - Trichirapalli



Languages

Tamil

Hindi

English